明晚我要跟我爸一起吃饭 你要来吗?
好啊，他很性感
不，我也会去
那么我们得想个暗号 如果一切进行的很顺利，你可以离开
不，我要你去那里支持我 我还没有告诉他我怀孕了
为什么?
因为我知道他会气炸了 我讨厌让他生气
瑞秋，这好像“爸爸别说教”
不，菲比，等一下，他是个可怕的人有次他抓到我抽烟
他说如果他再看到我抽烟 他会逼我吃下一整盒烟
我一定会去
天啊，我不会让那个男人逼你吃掉你的宝宝
那个家伙是谁? 我想我认识他
才怪
天啊，莫妮卡 他是你单身女郎派对上的脱衣舞男
什么?
你的秘密单身女郎派对
- 你办了单身女郎派对?
- 她用牙齿解开他的丁字裤
快阻止我
我们不办单身汉或单身女郎派对 我们都同意那是愚蠢的传统
那是个很棒的传统
抱歉，她们给我一个大惊喜 我真的没有办法
你可以用手解开它
这太不公平了 我想帮我最好的朋友办单身汉派对
却不能那么做我们只能一起去吃牛排
你跟女服务生一起回家
对，那一晚真的很美妙
我不敢相信你没有告诉我
你知道在婚姻里开放跟诚实是很重要的
我就知道送你那本书有一天我一定会被报应
老友记 Friends S08E08 本集播出：脱衣舞娘
- 我帮大家点了摩洛哥鸡肉
- 我不吃肉
它是鸡肉
- 我也不吃那个
- 我一直都搞不懂女同志
- 宝贝，告诉我你有什么事
- 事实上…
你的74年拉费红酒国际葡萄酒五大名品之一）
我点的是75年的红酒 它的味道很棒，74年的酒烂透了(就像阴沟水)
你为什么要给我那么烂的酒(阴沟水)?
那是个难题吗? 你是白痴吗? 所以你才会来当服务生吗?
那就是为什么我告诉经理我不想为你服务的原因
少来了，别那么幼稚
你应该注意到了他真的很可怕
但他说的对 74年的酒真的很难喝
这是个天大的错误菲比，我不敢告诉他
瑞秋…
我得等上几年然后宝宝会告诉他
为什么?让他可以对宝宝生气?
- 那是宝宝的问题
- 服务生没问题吧?
- 我不知道，我去了洗手间
亲爱的，你得告诉我 最近你有什么新鲜事
我有TIVo啊（互动式数字录放影机）
-什么是TIVo
-就是怀孕的意思
不然你约我来做什么?
你真的怀孕了?
对跟不对
但不对是不对的答案
总而言之，对
孩子的爸爸是谁? 不，拜托，别告诉就是她
不，是罗斯，你喜欢罗斯
爸爸 我希望你能接受这件事
想一想，这是件好事这是你第一个外孙
你要当外公了
没错，我要当外公了
我要当外公了
- 婚礼什么时候举行?
- 谁的婚礼?
婚礼你们得举行婚礼
小姑娘，你休想坐在那里告诉我 我的第一个外孙会是个私生子
- 告诉我你们会举行婚礼
- 二月二日
今天去看你上课我觉得很酷
谢谢，虽然我觉得你看起来像是睡着了
不，我闭上了眼睛要专心听你说话
我很多学生都会那么做
- 我得走了
- 今晚见?
谢谢你让我参观你收集的半宝石 它真的很棒
天啊，你的床上功夫一定很厉害
你跟蒙娜交往了一阵子 情况如何?
很不错
我们处得很好 她很…
- 辣?
- 我本来说很温柔，但你答对了
她能接受宝宝的事?
我还没有告诉她 我不想吓跑她
你得老实说，不然的话 你以为你们的方向一样，
事实上你们在走不一样的路
我会拿那本书 把你打死
天啊 你一定会爱死我了
很好，因为到目前为止 在这段婚姻里我真的很喜欢你
好吧，关于单身女郎派对的事 我真的很难过…
所以今晚你要办单身汉派对
我在餐厅的同事给我这个电话号码 我雇了一个脱衣舞娘来跳舞给你看
我可以进太太名人堂了吧?
- 甜心，这太疯狂了，我不要脱衣舞娘
- 你能让她说完吗?
来吧，一定会很好玩的 它会让我觉得好过一点
我帮你们准备了派对帽跟喇叭
抛开我爸爸跟魔术师上床那段不谈
这简直就是重演我14岁的生日派对
听着，我很感激，但它有点可怕我已经不是单身汉了
别把它当成是单身汉派对 把它当成是结婚两个月的礼物
当然，结婚一年是纸婚两个月的话可以看热舞
拜托，我觉得好难过 去看看那个辣妹脱光衣服吧
- 好吧，但我这么做是为了你
- 太帅了
还有乔伊
- 谢谢，你还想邀请谁?
- 光罗斯跟乔伊就够丢脸了
抱歉，我没办法去 今晚我跟蒙娜有约
谁会为了假单身汉派对取消真正的约会?
抱歉 我得取消今晚的约会，宝贝
抱歉我无法参加你想像出来的婚礼 那天我很忙
我得参加独角兽受洗礼跟小精灵的戒酒会
我知道，我乱了方寸
我不要他对着我大叫 把我当成74年拉图红酒（国际葡萄酒五大名品之一）
是拉菲
74年拉飞红酒喝起来真的很不错
好吧，他来了，我得告诉他我得很坚强
我刚刚打了电话给一个朋友
我想或许我可以在这么短的时间内订到广场饭店
真的吗?
广场饭店?
爸爸
- 爸爸，我得跟你谈一谈
- 什么事? 宝贝
我们不会举行婚礼 罗斯跟我不会结婚
- 对不起，爸爸
- 我不敢相信
- 爸爸，请保持冷静
- 你怎么能要我保持冷静?
我完全无法接受，瑞秋 我要知道为什么
因为那个混蛋不愿意娶你吗?
- 是那样吗?
- 对，他说我是瑕疵品
快结婚了 你很紧张吧?
你在做什么?
我们假装这是你结婚前的单身汉派对，那样比较好玩
好吧，我不敢相信明天是我的大喜之日
知道你永远无法跟别的女人在一起 你有什么感觉?
知道你每天醒过来都会看到同一张脸．
直到死神来拯救你
你说的对，这样比较好玩
她来了，快点
哪个幸运儿是钱德?
是我
乔伊崔比亚尼，你的头号仰慕者
- 那是卧房吗?
- 对，就在那边
好吧，你准备好就进来
那好奇怪
- 她为什么要到卧房去?
- 我在等着
- 她是…
- 她是脱光衣服的妓女
我喜欢你家 这玩意从哪里来的?
那是在加尔各答买的18世纪印度工艺品
哇
原来你不只哈恐龙的事
一点都没错
天啊，我很抱歉
算了，那是在皮尔第一进出口公司（著名的工艺品杂货店）买的
抱歉
你以为你可以搞大我女儿的肚子然后不娶她吗?
我要杀了你
事实上 我现在真的很不方便
快一点解释给我听，盖勒
- 你先让我的瑞秋怀孕
- 你让瑞秋怀孕?
- 谁干的
- 就是你
没错，但那是一夜情 那毫无意义
真的吗? 我女儿对你来说毫无意义?
不是的，她对我来说意义重大 我在乎…我爱瑞秋
- 什么?
- 但不是那样的
我没有爱上她 我把她当成朋友
你就是那样对待朋友的吗? 你搞大她的肚子又不肯娶她?
我有跟她求婚 但我不想那么做
为什么? 因为你想跟这个荡妇鬼混?
荡妇?
抱歉，葛林医生，蒙娜 蒙娜，葛林医生
我不敢相信里面有个脱光衣服的妓女
或许她是妓女兼脱衣舞娘…
但她会搞不清楚该做什么
有可能，技术上来说她脱光了衣服 只是我们没看到
小姐
你也是脱衣舞娘吗?
不是，但我可以假装 那得另外收钱
这是另外收钱的项目 手拷，鞭打…
或许莫妮卡是在跟你开玩笑
帮自己老公找妓女 那真的很好笑
那很好笑，或许我生日的时候她会去杀人
我敢说罗斯也知情他“刚好”很忙
- 你不介意我抽烟吧?
- 事实上我想…
抽吧，反正我们会烧掉那个房间
- 你为什么一直没有告诉我？
- 我打算告诉你，但是...
你以为你可以得到你要的 然后像甩了瑞秋一样甩掉她
我没有甩掉瑞秋 我们也没有在一起
我可以…
让答录机接吧
罗斯，我是乔伊 这里有个妓女
我们想或许你知情
不
我需要躺一下
大伙们，我能跟你们谈一下吗?
听着，我要你们推销鸭肉特餐
因为如果客人不吃鸭肉你们得吃，它不是很好吃
今晚是单身汉派对之夜?
- 谢谢你给我那个女孩的电话号码
- 别客气，谁要办派对?
- 我老公
- 你帮你老公雇了一个妓女
- 她是脱衣舞娘
- 不，她是妓女
- 他们不是有时这样称呼脱衣舞娘?
- 因为她们是妓女
天啊 史都，我不敢相信你会这么做
你确定她是妓女?
如果不是的话 她是我约过最棒跟最贵的女孩
或许她是故意帮你雇了个妓女
她为什么要那么做?
或许她要你好好学一学
你在床上表现的不好吗?
这是最糟糕的单身汉派对
- 你们怎么那么久?
- 再一分钟就好
“一分钟” 一分钟内会发生什么事?
好吧 或许你该去请她离开
- 为什么是我?
- 这是你的单身汉派对
- 所以应该是你去说
- 我不要，你去
好吧，剪刀石头布决定谁去请那个妓女离开
- 什么?
- 我想念这个
我想我们以前没有这么做过
不，我想念跟你鬼混的日子
- 我们还是混在一起
- 跟以前不一样了
还记得吗? 你跟我我们以前老是黏在一起
现在一切都变得不一样了
一切的确不一样了 我结婚了
别误会我 我为你们感到高兴
我只是想念我们一起鬼混的日子，你知道吗?
我也是
听我说，从现在开始我们找时间一起出去
你说的对，过来
天啊
听着 我差一点就要洗劫你们了
她是妓女 她是…
嗨，我们通过电话
你爸到过我家
他是个好人
- 不
- 我得走了
我只是要到这里来 我不想错过吵架场面
罗斯，我很抱歉
我发誓明天我会亲自跟他把事情讲清楚
或是透过电子邮件
我不在乎你爸，我在乎蒙娜当时她在场，她气疯了
好吧，我也会跟她解释 告诉我她的电子邮件信箱
我发誓我会解决的我发誓我会跟她说
好吧，谢谢你
就那样? 你们说那是吵架?
“我们要分手了”，“不，我们没有” 你们两个是怎么了?
谢谢你答应回来
很好，你在这里
我很担心 这会是个不愉快的经验
不，蒙娜，听我说
首先我很抱歉 我爸对你大叫
但我听说你控制住自己的脾气 你得告诉我你是怎么做的
- 说重点
- 好吧
罗斯跟我以前交往过
我们的确有宝宝了
但我们绝对不可能复合
- 我怎么能相信你的话?
- 因为我们把彼此逼疯了
他占有欲很强，爱吃醋 他从来不会忘了那些小事
试着去跟这个女人交往吧
但那都比不上他的温柔体贴．
跟善良
或许你不该碰我
我不想介入这么复杂的事
我明白，但是蒙娜 哪段感情不复杂呢?
我们都有自己的包袱 你也一样
不然你为什么还是单身呢?
我得走了
我应该让门开着吗?
我还不确定你为什么不告诉我？
因为那跟我对你的感觉 没有关系
- 你还是应该告诉我
- 我知道，我打算那么做，
但我想最好 还是让瑞秋的爸爸来告诉你
我犯了一个错…
但那是因为我真的很喜欢你，真的
好吧，我想你可以把门关上了
我忘了拿皮包 你们和好了
他是接吻高手，对吧？ 我要走了
我发誓我不知道她是妓女
你让她在这里抽烟?
你奶奶的被单上还有她的屁股印子 你真的想谈抽烟的事?
你知道吗? 我要补偿你
我答应要帮你请脱衣舞娘...
我一定会做到
- 莫妮卡，等一下
- 什么?
继续
这双网球鞋好紧
- 我想把它们脱掉
- 麻烦你别说话
知道了，帅哥
只因为你不爱这个家伙…
- 你跟你爸说实话了
- 大约是一小时前
- 你想去看电影吗?
- 好
再见，爸爸
我无法接受 爱跟这件事有什么关系?
还有比爱更重要的事
你得考虑宝宝
你得想想 你做的决定会有什么后果
我的确会想我做的决定会有什么后果
你有什么权利…
去死吧
讲电话的男人真是笨蛋
Hey, I'm having dinner with my dad tomorrow night.
Do you wanna come?
Sure, yeah. He's kind of sexy.
Oh, no, I'll be there too.
So we'll come up with some kind of signal.
If it's going well, you can take off.
No, I just need you there for support.
I haven't told him that I'm pregnant yet.
Oh. Why not?
Because I know he's gonna flip out, and I hate it when he's angry.
Rachel, this is all so "Papa Don't Preach."
No, Phoeb, wait. He's a scary guy.
I mean, one time he caught me smoking.
He said if he ever saw me doing that again, he'd make me eat the entire pack.
Wow. Well, I will be there.
Gosh, I'm not gonna let that man make you eat your baby!
Hey, who is that guy? I think I know him.
No, you don't.
Oh, my God! Monica, he's the stripper from your bachelorette party!
Her what?
Your secret bachelorette party.
- You had a bachelorette party?
- She untied his G-string with her teeth.
Somebody stop me!
We weren't having bachelor, bachelorette parties.
We agreed that it's a silly tradition.
It's a grand tradition!
I'm sorry. They surprised me. There was nothing I could do.
Well, you could've untied it with your hands.
- This is so unfair.
- The one thing I wanted was to throw my best friend a bachelor party...
...but I wasn't allowed. All we got was a stupid steak dinner.
You went home with the waitress.
Yeah, that was a pretty good night.
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
You know that the two pillars of marriage are openness and honesty.
I knew giving you that book was gonna come back and bite me in the ass.
The One With The Stripper
- I'll order everyone the Moroccan chicken.
- Oh, I don't eat meat.
It's chicken!
- I don't eat that either.
- I never understand you lesbians.
- So, baby, tell me, what's new with you?
- Well, actually...
Your '74 Lafite, sir.
I ordered the '75. That's a magnificent wine.
The '74 is sewage!
Why would you bring me sewage?
Is that a hard question?
Are you an idiot? Is that why you're a waiter?
This is why I told the manager I wouldn't wait on you.
Oh, come on. Don't be such a baby.
In case you didn't notice, that is a scary man.
He's right, though. The '74 is absolute piss.
This was such a huge mistake.
I can't tell him, Phoebe. I can't.
Rachel...
I'm gonna wait a couple of years, and then the baby will tell him.
- Why? So he can get mad at the baby?
- Hey, that is the baby's problem.
- Everything okay with the waiter?
- I have no idea. I went to the bathroom.
So, sweetie, you were starting to tell me what is new with you.
I got TiVo.
- What's TiVo?
- It's slang for "pregnant."
Well, what were you thinking asking me to come?
Are you really pregnant?
Well, yes and no.
Except, not no.
So to sum it up, yeah.
Who is the father?
Oh, no. Please don't tell me it's her.
No, it's Ross. It's Ross. You like Ross.
Daddy, I hope you're okay with all of this.
Think about it. This is a good thing.
This is your first grandchild!
You're gonna be a poppy!
That's true. I'm a poppy!
I'm gonna be a poppy!
- So when is the wedding?
- The who?
The wedding. There's going to be a wedding.
Young lady, don't you sit there and tell me my first grandchild is gonna be a bastard!
- Tell me there's gonna be a wedding!
- February 2nd!
It was cool seeing you lecture today.
Thanks. Although it kind of seemed like you were falling asleep.
No, I had my eyes closed so I could concentrate and, you know, take it all in.
Yeah, a lot of my students do that.
- I've got to get going.
- Okay, I'll see you tonight?
Thanks for showing me your semiprecious-stone collection. It's amazing.
My God, you must be good in bed.
So you and Mona, it's been a while now. How's it going?
It's good. It's going good.
I mean, we get along great. She's so...
- Hot?
- I was gonna say sweet, but yeah!
She's okay with the baby?
I haven't actually told her yet.
I don't wanna scare her off.
You have to be honest. Otherwise, you may think you're going down the same path...
...but you're really going down different ones.
I'm gonna take that book and I'm gonna beat you to death with it.
Oh, my God, you are gonna love me so much.
Oh, good. Because so far in this marriage, I just like you a lot.
All right. I felt bad about the bachelorette party thing...
...so tonight you're gonna have a bachelor party.
I got this number from this guy at work and I hired a stripper to come dance for you.
Am I going in the wife hall of fame or what?
- Honey, that's crazy. I don't want a stripper.
- Will you let the lady talk?
Come on, it'll be fun.
It'll make me feel so much better.
I got you party hats and porn.
Throw in my father making out with the magician...
...and it's just like my 14th birthday all over again.
Look, I appreciate it, but it's a little creepy.
I'm not a bachelor anymore.
Don't think of it as a bachelor party.
Think of it as a two-month anniversary present.
Sure. One year is paper, but two months is lap dance.
Please, I feel so bad. Just watch the hot woman get naked!
- Fine, but I'm only doing this for you.
- Yeah!
And Joey.
- Thank you. Who else do you wanna invite?
- Ross and Joey is embarrassing enough.
Actually, sorry, I can't even make it.
I'm seeing Mona tonight.
Who would cancel an actual date just to go to a fake bachelor party?
I'm sorry. I gotta cancel tonight, baby.
I'm sorry I won't make it to your imaginary wedding, but I'm busy that day.
I already have a unicorn baptism and a leprechaun bar mitzvah.
I know, I know. I panicked.
I didn't want him to start yelling at me like I was some '74 Latour.
It's Lafite.
The '74 Latour is actually drinking quite nicely.
All right, here he comes. I'm gonna tell him. I'm gonna be strong.
I just called a friend of mine.
I think I may be able to book The Plaza on short notice.
Really?
The Plaza?
Oh, Daddy!
- Right. Daddy, I need to talk to you.
- What is it, sweetie?
There's not gonna be a wedding.
Ross and I aren't getting married.
- I'm sorry, Daddy.
- I don't believe this!
- Daddy, stay calm, please.
- How do you expect me to stay calm?
This is unacceptable, Rachel. And I wanna know why!
Is it because that punk won't marry you?
- Is that it?
- Yes. He says I'm damaged goods.
You nervous about getting married?
What are you doing?
Let's pretend it's a real bachelor party, before your wedding.
It'll be more fun.
All right. I can't believe tomorrow's the big day.
How's it feel knowing you're never gonna be with another woman?
Knowing you're gonna have to wake up to the same face every day...
...until you finally have the sweet release of death.
You're right. This is more fun.
That's her! Okay, come on!
Which one of you lucky boys is Chandler?
That's me!
That's me.
Joey Tribbiani. Big fan.
- Is that a bedroom?
- Yeah, right over there.
All right. Whenever you're ready.
That was weird.
- Why would she go in the bedroom?
- I'm waiting.
- So she's a...
- Yeah, that's one naked hooker.
I love your place. Where is this guy from?
That's an 18th-century Indian artifact from Calcutta.
Oh. Wow.
So you're more than just dinosaurs.
So much more.
Oh, my God! I am so sorry!
Forget it. It's from Pier 1.
Sorry.
You think you can knock up my daughter and then not marry her?
I'm gonna kill you!
You know, this is actually not a great time for me.
So come on. Explain yourself, Geller.
- First, you get my Rachel pregnant.
- You got Rachel pregnant?
- Who did?
- You did!
Yes, I did, but it was a one-night thing. It meant nothing.
Oh? Really? That's what my daughter means to you, nothing?
No, sir. She means a lot to me.
I care... I love Rachel.
- What?
- But not that way.
I'm not in love with her. I love her like a friend.
That's how you treat a friend, get her in trouble and refuse to marry her?
Hey, I offered to marry her. But I didn't want to.
Well, why not? So you could spend your time with this tramp?
Tramp?
I'm sorry. Dr. Green, Mona. Mona, Dr. Green.
I can't believe there is a naked hooker in there!
Maybe she's a hooker and a stripper...
...but she got confused about what to do.
Could be. I mean, technically, she did strip.
We just missed it.
Ma'am?
Are you also a stripper?
No, but I can pretend to strip.
But that's gonna cost extra.
Okay, here's the extras: Handcuffs, spanking...
Maybe Monica's playing a joke on you.
Getting her own husband a hooker. That's pretty funny.
That is funny. Maybe for my birthday she'll murder someone.
I'll bet Ross was in on it too. I mean, he was "conveniently" busy.
- Do you mind if I smoke in here?
- Actually, I'd rather...
Yeah, go ahead. We're gonna have to burn that room down anyway.
- How could you have kept all this from me?
- I was going to tell you, but...
You figure you'd get what you wanted, then you'd dump her like you did Rachel.
Hey, I did not dump Rachel. Nor are we still together.
Can I...?
Why don't we just let the machine get that.
Hey, Ross, it's Joey.
There's a hooker over here...
...and we thought maybe you'd know something about it.
No! No! No!
No!
I need to lie down.
Hey, guys, can I talk to you for a minute?
Listen, again, I want to urge you to push the duck special...
...because if they don't eat the duck, you're going to, and it's not very good.
Tonight's the night of the big bachelor party?
- Thanks for giving me that girl's number.
- No problem. Say, who's the party for?
- For my husband.
- You hired your husband a hooker?
- She's a stripper.
- No, she's a hooker.
- Is that what they call strippers sometimes?
- When they're hookers.
Oh, my God. Stu, I can't believe you did this.
Now, you're sure she's a hooker?
It's either that, or she's just the best, most expensive date I ever had.
Maybe she meant to get you a hooker.
Why would she do that?
Maybe she wants you to learn something.
Is there anything you're really bad at, you know, sexually?
This is the worst bachelor party ever.
- What's taking you boys so long?
- In a minute!
"In a minute"? What's gonna happen in a minute?
All right. Maybe you should ask her to leave.
- Why me?
- Hey, it's your bachelor party.
- Which is why you should do it.
- I don't want to. You do it.
All right. Rock, paper, scissors for who has to tell the whore to leave.
- What?
- I miss this.
I don't think we've actually done this before.
No, I miss hanging out with you.
- We still hang out.
- Not like we used to.
Remember? You and me, we used to be inseparable.
You know, now it's like things are different.
Well, you know, things are different. I'm married now.
And, hey, don't get me wrong, I am so happy for you guys.
I just miss hanging out. Just us, you know?
Yeah, I miss that too.
I'll tell you what. From now on, we'll make time to hang out.
You got it. Come here.
Oh, God.
Listen, I am this close to robbing you guys.
She's a hooker! She's a hooker! She's a...
Hi. We spoke on the phone.
So your dad dropped by.
He's a pleasant man.
- Oh, no.
- I better go.
Just over here. I don't wanna miss the fight.
Ross, I am so sorry.
I promise, I will straighten this out with him tomorrow, in person.
Or via e-mail.
I don't care about your dad. I care about Mona.
She was there and she's freaked out!
Okay, I'll fix that too. What's her e-mail address?
All right, I promise, I'll fix this. I swear. I'll talk to her.
Okay. Thank you.
That's it? You call that a fight?
"We were on a break!" "No, we weren't!" What happened to you two?
Thank you so much for coming back over.
Oh, good. You're here.
And I was worried that it was going to be uncomfortable.
No, Mona, just hear me out.
First of all, I am so sorry about my father yelling at you.
But I heard that you held your own. You have to tell me how you did that.
- Focus.
- Okay.
Yes, Ross and I used to date.
And yes, we are gonna have a baby.
But we are definitely not getting back together.
- How can I be sure of that?
- Because we drove each other crazy.
He was possessive, he was jealous.
He could never just let the little things go.
Trying to date this woman.
None of that compared to how kind and gentle...
...and thoughtful he is.
You probably shouldn't touch me.
I don't wanna get in the middle of something so complicated.
I get it, but, Mona, what relationship is not complicated?
We all have our baggage. You must too.
Why else would you still be single?
I'm so gonna leave right now.
Should I leave this open?
I'm not sure yet. Why didn't you just tell me about all this?
Because what's going on has nothing to do with how I feel about you.
- You still should have told me.
- I know, and I was going to...
...but I thought it was better that you heard it from Rachel's father.
I made a mistake...
...but it's only because I really, really like you. Really.
Okay. I guess you can close the door now.
Forgot my purse. Oh, you guys made up.
He's a good kisser, isn't he? I'm going!
I swear I didn't know she was a hooker.
Did you let her smoke in here?
Her ass-print is still on your grandmother's quilt.
Really want to talk about smoking?
You know what, I'm gonna make this up to you.
I promised you a stripper...
...and you're gonna get a stripper.
- Monica, wait.
- What?
Carry on.
These tennis shoes are so tight.
- I think I'll take them off.
- Could you not narrate?
Gotcha, sailor.
Just because you're not in love with the guy...
- You told your dad the truth.
- About an hour ago.
- Wanna go see a movie?
- Yes.
Bye, Dad.
It's unacceptable! What the hell does love have to do with it?
There are more important things than love.
You have to think about the baby.
You have to think about the consequences of your decisions!
Hey, I do think about the consequences of my decisions!
Well, what gives you the right to...?
Go to hell!
Stupid guy on my phone.